Hello everyone today I'll introduce my Antigravity IDE setup
First of all my vision for this IDE
is to build it into an all-in-one multimedia development center
meaning this is a versatile
multi-project centralized workspace
Taking game development as an example
it involves many distinct workflows
and when working within the IDE
it can be organized into distinct folders for management
Here I structured multiple project folders for a streamlined pipeline
where each workspace has its dedicated AI folder
to manage AI Rules and Skills
However during actual production
relying solely on the vanilla IDE with AI for planning and creation
revealed many friction points and limitations
So I built several native tools to solve these workflow challenges